lt100100'Segoe UI', Tahoma, sans-serifTahoma, sans-serif75%75%<html>
<head>
  <title></title>
</head>
<body>
</body>
</html>en-US,enISO-8859-1falseen-US55466048630702550550307025751650830ISO-8859-1,windows-1252http://tools.google.com/chrome/intl/en/welcome.html52https://chrome.google.com/webstore?hl=en&category=themehttps://chrome.google.com/webstore?hl=enhttps://chrome.google.com/webstore?hl=enhttp://www.google.com/chrome/intl/en/welcome.htmlhttp://gweb-gettingstartedguide.appspot.com/?hl=enhttp://www.adobe.com/go/settmgr_storage_enhttp://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager02.htmlhttp://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager06.htmlhttps://accounts.google.com/IssuedAuthSubTokens?hl=enhttps://support.google.com/accounts/bin/answer.py?answer=1070457https://www.google.com/support/chrome/bin/answer.py?answer=1181420761546156746570782681http://en.browser.baidu.comhttp://en.browser.baidu.com/forumhttp://en.browser.baidu.com/forumhttp://en.browser.baidu.com/report/feedback.cgihttp://en.browser.baidu.com/report/dump.cgihttp://en.browser.baidu.com/upgrade/upgrade.cgihttp://en.browser.baidu.com/report/active.cgihttp://en.browser.baidu.com/report/action.cgihttp://www.google.com/http://www.google.com/http://www.facebook.com/http://www.youtube.com/http://www.yahoo.com/http://www.wikipedia.org/http://www.live.com/http://www.twitter.com/http://www.amazon.com/http://www.pchome.com.tw/http://www.pantip.com/http://www.wretch.cc/http://www.pixnet.net/http://tw.hao123.com/?tn=spark_free_other_01_hao123_twhttp://en.hao123.com/http://www.hao123.com/http://www.google.com.tw/http://tw.yahoo.com/http://www.uol.com.br/http://www.globo.com/http://www.sanook.com/http://pantip.com/http://th.hao123.com/?tn=spark_free_other_01_hao123_thhttp://th.yahoo.com/http://www.google.co.th/http://br.hao123.com/?tn=spark_free_other_01_hao123_brhttp://br.yahoo.com/http://www.google.com.br/http://www.ask.com/http://www.ebay.com/http://www.linkedin.com/http://www.gamer.com.tw/http://www.udn.com/http://www.mercadolivre.com.br/http://www.4shared.com/http://www.dek-d.com/http://www.kapook.com/http://www.mthai.com/http://www.orkut.com/http://www.terra.com/http://www.yam.com/http://www.ruten.com.tw/http://www.baidu.com/http://www.qq.com/http://www.taobao.com/http://www.sina.com.cn/http://www.renren.com/http://www.weibo.com/http://www.tmall.com/http://www.youku.com/http://www.360buy.com/http://www.douban.com/http://www.163.com/http://www.google.co.id/http://www.blogger.com/http://id.yahoo.com/http://www.kashus.co.id/http://www.detik.com/http://id.wordpress.com/http://www.tokobagus.com/http://id.wikipedia.org/http://www.klikbca.com/http://dl.browser.baidu.com/assets/welcome/en/Times New RomanCourier NewTimes New RomanArialComic Sans MSImpactSegoe UI SymbolTimes New RomanCourier NewTimes New RomanArialTimes New RomanCourier NewTimes New RomanArialMS PGothicMS GothicMS PMinchoMS PGothicGulimGulimcheBatangGulimGungsuhSimsunNSimsunSimsunSimsunPMingLiUMingLiUPMingLiUPMingLiU161306(empty)Untitled WebpageAll Files$1 File (.$2)Select FolderSave FileOpen FileOpen FilesAll FilesPressCloseMinimizeMaximizeRestoreScroll to HereLeft EdgeRight EdgeTopBottomPage UpPage DownScroll LeftScroll RightScroll UpScroll Down&UndoCu&t&Copy&Paste&DeleteSelect &allOKCancelCloseEscTabInsHomeDelEndPgUpPgDwnLeft ArrowRight ArrowUp ArrowDown ArrowEnterF1F11BackspaceCtrl+$1Alt+$1Shift+$1Command+$1$1 B$1 KB$1 MB$1 GB$1 TB$1 PB$1 B/s$1 KB/s$1 MB/s$1 GB/s$1 TB/s$1 PB/sDisable extensionDisable notifications from $1NotificationsSettingsSettings...Clear AllYou have no notifications. Relax!Quiet modeExit quiet modeQuiet mode for one hourQuiet mode for one daySparkSparkSparkSpark is a web browser that runs webpages and applications with lightning speed. It's fast, stable, and easy to use. Browse the web more safely with malware and phishing protection built into Spark.Spark App Launcher is a standalone platform for Chrome apps.Spark FrameSpark App LauncherSpark BinariesSpark Frame Update.Spark Frame has been updated. Please relaunch your browser. Spark version: %ls, Spark Frame version: %lsUnknown version.About Spark Frame...http://www.google.com/support/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=161796This site recommends Spark Frame (already installed).New windowWindows error detectedYour computer is missing some important Windows system files, so Spark will be unable to function correctly.InstantIn this case, the address listed in the certificate does not match the address of the website your browser tried to go to. One possible reason for this is that your communications are being intercepted by an attacker who is presenting a certificate for a different website, which would cause a mismatch. Another possible reason is that the server is set up to return the same certificate for multiple websites, including the one you are attempting to visit, even though that certificate is not valid for all of those websites. Spark can say for sure that you reached <strong>$1</strong>, but cannot verify that that is the same site as <strong>$2</strong> which you intended to reach. If you proceed, Spark will not check for any further name mismatches.You attempted to reach <strong>$1</strong>, but the server presented an expired certificate. No information is available to indicate whether that certificate has been compromised since its expiration. This means Spark cannot guarantee that you are communicating with <strong>$2</strong> and not an attacker. Your computer's clock is currently set to $3. Does that look right? If not, you should correct the error and refresh this page.You attempted to reach <strong>$1</strong>, but the server presented a certificate that is not yet valid. No information is available to indicate whether that certificate can be trusted. Spark cannot reliably guarantee that you are communicating with <strong>$2</strong> and not an attacker. Your computer's clock is currently set to $3. Does that look right? If not, you should correct your system's clock and then refresh this page.You attempted to reach <strong>$1</strong>, but the server presented a certificate issued by an entity that is not trusted by your computer's operating system. This may mean that the server has generated its own security credentials, which Spark cannot rely on for identity information, or an attacker may be trying to intercept your communications.You attempted to reach <strong>$1</strong>, but the certificate that the server presented contains errors. Spark cannot use a certificate with errors and cannot validate the identity of the site that you have attempted to connect to.Task Manager - SparkSpark didn't shut down correctly. To reopen the pages you had open, click Restore.$1 - SparkGet help with using SparkBaidu Inc.Copyright (C) 2013 Baidu Inc. All Rights Reserved.Chromium is made possible by the <a target="_blank" href="$1">Chromium</a> open source project and other <a target="_blank" href="$2">open source software</a>.Not used in Spark. Placeholder to keep resource maps in sync. It expects one argument: $1.SparkSpark ToolbarSpark is unresponsive. Relaunch now?Spark is now importing the following items from $1:Find your bookmarks in the Spark menu or on the bookmarks bar.Sadly, your Mozilla Firefox settings are not available while that browser is running. To import those settings to Spark, save your work and close all Firefox windows. Then click Continue.Please close all Spark windows and try again.Please close all Spark windows (including those in Windows 8 mode) and try again.Are you sure you want to uninstall Spark?Uninstall SparkUninstall Spark App LauncherWelcome to SparkStart SparkMake Spark the default browserWelcome to SparkSpark's New Tab page has been remodeled. Switch between sections by clicking these labels. Spark will remember your preference for next time.Spark needs to launch an external application to handle $1 links. The link requested is $2.Spark requires Windows XP or later. Some features may not work.Spark does not support $1.Please close all Spark windows and relaunch Spark for this change to take effect.Let Spark run in the backgroundContinue running background apps when Spark is closedSpark cannot read and write to its data directory:

$1Optional: Help make Spark better by automatically sending usage statistics and crash reports to Baidu.Your profile can not be used because it is from a newer version of Spark.

Some features may be unavailable. Please specify a different profile directory or use a newer version of Spark.Your preferences can not be read.

Some features may be unavailable and changes to preferences won't be saved.Your preferences file is corrupt or invalid.

Spark is unable to recover your settings.SparkWhoa! Spark has crashed. Relaunch now?Do you want Spark to save your password?Spark uses your default search engine, which is currently set to $1. Do you want to keep your default search engine?Exit SparkAn administrator has installed Spark on this system, and it is available for all users. The system-level Spark will replace your user-level installation now.This computer already has a more recent version of Spark. If the software is not working, please uninstall Spark and try again.This computer already has a more recent version of the Spark components. Please use a more recent installer.This computer already has a more recent version of Spark Frame. If the software is not working, please uninstall Spark Frame and try again.This computer already has a more recent version of Spark and Spark Frame. If the software is not working, please uninstall both Spark and Spark Frame and try again.Spark Frame is already installed and available to all users of this computer. If you want to install Spark Frame at the user level, you must first uninstall the system-level version installed by an administrator.Installation failed due to unspecified error. If Spark is currently running, please close it and try again.Can not install the same Spark version that is currently running. Please close Spark and try again.Can not install the same Spark Frame version that is currently running. Please close Spark Frame and try again.Installation failed due to unspecified error. Please download Spark again.Spark requires Windows Vista or Windows XP with SP2 or higher.An operating system error occurred during installation. Please download Spark again.The installer couldn't create a temporary directory. Please check for free disk space and permission to install software.The installer failed to uncompress archive. Please download Spark again.The installer archive is corrupted or invalid. Please download Spark again.You do not have appropriate rights for system-level install. Try running the installer again as Administrator.No installation of Spark or Spark Frame found to update.A conflict with another installed application has been detected.Uninstallation complete.Spark installation directory seems to be in use. Please reboot your computer and try again.A conflicting installation of Spark or Spark Frame was found on the system. Please uninstall it and try again.A conflicting installation of Spark or Spark Frame was found on the system. Please uninstall it and try again.Invalid arguments. Spark Frame cannot be installed in ready mode without also installing Spark.Spark may use web services to improve your browsing experience.Spark is now importing Favorites/Bookmarks.Internet BrowserAccess the InternetLaunch Chromium appsAlso delete your browsing data?Change default browser to:UninstallSpark isn't your default browser.There is a new version of Spark available.There's a new version of Spark available, and it's faster than ever.There's a new, safer version of Spark available.Spark has been updated, but you haven't used it for at least 30 days.Spark lets you click a phone number on the web and call it with Skype!Try it out, it's already installedDon't bug meWhy am I seeing this?Modules loaded into SparkThis module is known to conflict with Spark.A module with the same name has been known to conflict with Spark.Crash reporting is not available in Spark.You are viewing a secure Spark page.Spark does not include the PDF viewer which is required for Print Preview to function.Adding to Spark...A download is currently in progress. Do you want to exit Spark and cancel the download?Downloads are currently in progress. Do you want to exit Spark and cancel the downloads?Yes, exit SparkSpark is configured to automatically launch when you start your computer.Allow signing into Spark.Your changes will take effect the next time you relaunch Spark.Show Spark App Launcher.Show a shortcut to the Spark App Launcher in the Windows TaskBar.Spark has stopped updating and no longer supports this version of your operating system.Summary of memory used by currently active browsers. For browsers which use multiple processes, memory reflects aggregate memory used across all browser processes.

For Spark, processes used to display diagnostics information (such as this "about:memory") are excluded.Nearly up-to-date! Relaunch Spark to finish updating.Spark is up to date.Updating Spark...Add to Spark$1 has been added to Spark.<b>Warning:</b> Spark cannot prevent extensions from recording your browsing history. To disable this extension in incognito mode, unselect this option.Remove from SparkAbout &SparkUpdate &SparkSee <a target="_blank" href="$1">more benefits</a> of signing in to Spark.You were previously signed in with a different account, signing in will merge your data. Consider creating a new Spark user via the <a href="spark://settings/search#Users" target="_parent">settings page</a> for your Spark stuff.You're signed in to Spark!Use this Google Account to sync all your Spark stuff?You're now signed in to Spark! Your bookmarks, history, and other settings will be synced to your Google Account.Sign in to SparkYou were signed in to Spark as $1. Please use the same account to sign in again.Someone previously signed in to Spark on this computer as $1. If that isn't your account, create a new Spark user to keep your information separate.

Signing in anyway will merge Spark information like bookmarks, history, and other settings to $2.Important information regarding your Spark dataYou are signing in with a managed account and giving its administrator control over your Spark profile. Your Spark data, such as your apps, bookmarks, history, passwords, and other settings will become permanently tied to $1. You will be able to delete this data via the Google Accounts Dashboard, but you will not be able to associate this data with another account.If you prefer to keep your existing Spark data separate, you can create a new Spark user for $1.Link my Spark data to this accountSpark Autofill settingsSave details in SparkAdd to SparkTry disabling network prediction by following these steps:
        Go to
        <strong>
        the Spark menu >
        <span jscontent="settingsTitle"></span>
        >
        <span jscontent="advancedTitle"></span>
        </strong>
        and deselect "<span jscontent="noNetworkPredictionTitle"></span>."
        If this does not resolve the issue, we recommend selecting this option
        again for improved performance.Go to
          <strong>
          the Spark menu >
          <span jscontent="settingsTitle"></span>
          >
          <span jscontent="advancedTitle"></span>
          >
          <span jscontent="proxyTitle"></span>
          >
          LAN Settings
          </strong>
          and deselect the "Use a proxy server for your LAN" checkbox.Spark App LauncherUse the Spark App Launcher to launch your apps.Sign in to SparkYou need to be signed into Spark to use apps. This allows Spark to sync your apps, bookmarks, history, passwords and other settings across devices.New background app added$1 will launch at system startup and continue to run in the background even once you've closed all other $2 windows.$1 has crashed. Click this balloon to restart the app.$1 has crashed. Click this balloon to reload the extension.No background apps runningNew site permissions settings will take effect after reloading the page.ReloadAllowed by policyBlocked by policyAllowed by extensionBlocked by extensionAllowed by youBlocked by youAllowed by defaultBlocked by defaultAsk by defaultPermissionsCookies and site dataallowblockaskGlobal defaultAllowedBlockedAskImagesJavaScriptPopupsPluginsLocationNotificationsFullscreenMouse LockMediaManage permission settingsShow cookies and site dataConnectionPermissionsIdentityConnectionIdentity verifiedIdentity not verifiedOthers$1 ($2 allowed / $3 blocked)Use global default (Allow)Use global default (Block)Use global default (Ask)Always allow on this siteAlways block on this siteUse global default ($1)Always $1$1:Show Full HistoryCustomize and control $1Did you mean to go to $1?HistoryDownloadsUntitledLoading...Edit items...Done removing itemsRemove selected itemsClear browsing data...Are you sure you want to delete these pages from your history?

Psst! Incognito mode $1 may come in handy next time.Loading...$1 - $2$1 to $2No search results found.No history entries found.All the pages you visit will appear here unless you open them in an incognito window. You can use the Search button on this page to search all the pages in your history.Search historyNewestNewerOlderSearch results for '$1'History(Cont.)ActionsRemove from historyMore from this siteGroup domainsShowall time visitsweekly visitsmonthly visitsToday($1)OKCancelAddUndo Delete&EditLearn moreCloseDoneSkipTabSave&Back&ForwardSave &as...P&rint...&View page sourceOpen link with...Configure...View page &infoI&nspect elementInspect &background pageRe&loadReload pageSimulate browser restartRe&load app&Translate to $1Reload frameSave &frame as...P&rint frame...&View frame sourceView frame &infoOpen link in new &tabOpen link in new &windowOpen link in inco&gnito windowSave lin&k as...Copy link addr&essCopy &email addressSa&ve image as...C&opy image URLCop&y imageOpen &image in new tab&Loop&Play&Pause&MuteUn&muteShow &controlsRotate &clockwiseRotate c&ounterclockwiseSa&ve video as...C&opy video URL&Open video in new tabSa&ve audio as...C&opy audio URL&Open audio in new tab&Undo&RedoCu&t&Copy&Paste&Delete&Add to dictionary&No spelling suggestionsAsk Google for suggestionsEnableNo thanksLoading suggestionNo more suggestions from GoogleAutomatically correct spellingSelect &all&Search $1 for '$2'&Go to $1Add as search en&gine...Input &methodsRun this plug-inHide this plug-inInstall missing plug-inVoice recognition optionsBlock offensive wordsAbout voice recognitionSpark can provide smarter spell-checking by sending what you type in the browser to Google servers, allowing you to use the same spell-checking technology used by Google search.&Spell-checker optionsCheck the spelling of text fields&Show spelling panel&Hide spelling panel&Language settings...Paste as plain textNew &tab&Show as tab&New windowNew &incognito windowPin this page to Start screen...Unpin this page from Start screen...Edit&UndoCu&t&Copy&Paste&DeleteSelect &all&Find...Save page &as...&Print...Too&lsMore too&ls&ZoomZoom&Larger+&Normal&Smaller−$1%&EncodingAuto detectMake Text LargerMake Text Smaller$1 ($2)UnicodeWesternChinese SimplifiedChinese TraditionalKoreanJapaneseThaiCentral EuropeanCyrillicGreekBalticSouth EuropeanNordicCelticRomanianTurkishArabicHebrewVietnameseView s&ource&Report an issue...&Developer tools&JavaScript console&File manager&Task managerR&eopen closed tabR&eopen closed windowMinimizeRestoreMaximizeClose&Show bookmarks barRequest tablet site&HistoryImport bookmarks and settings...&Profiling enabled&Full screenFull screen&Clear browsing data...&Downloads&Extensions&Settings&OptionsH&elpView incompatibilitiesView background pages ($1)E&xit - $1 SearchSearch $1 for $2Run $1 command: $2<enter query>(Keyword: $1)&Edit search engines...Search enginesKeywordNameName:Keyword:URL:Insert %s in the URL where the search terms should appear.Make defaultEdit Search EngineAdd Search EngineTitle must contain at least one characterMust be a valid URLKeyword must be empty or uniqueDefault search settingsOther search enginesSearch engines added by extensions$1 (Default)# secs# secNANANANA# mins# minNANANANA# hours# hourNANANANA# days# dayNANANANA# secs left# sec leftNANANANA# mins left# min leftNANANANA# minutes left# minute leftNANANANA# hours left# hour leftNANANANA# days left# day leftNANANANA# seconds# secondNANANANA# minutes# minuteNANANANA# secs ago# sec agoNANANANA# mins ago# min agoNANANANA# hours ago# hour agoNANANANA# days ago# day agoNANANANATodayYesterdayShow all downloads...Download errorInsufficient permissionsCannot save due to insufficient permissions. Please save to another location.Path too longThe file path or name is too long.  Please save with a shorter name or to another location.Disk fullYour hard disk is full.  Please save to another location or make more room on the hard disk.File too largeThe file is too large for your computer to handle. Sorry.System busyYour computer is doing too many things right now.  Try again later.Virus detectedAnti-virus software detected a virus.BlockedSecurity settings on your computer blocked this file.Virus scan failedAnti-virus software failed unexpectedly while scanning this file.File truncatedDestination file was truncated or removed since last download.Network timeoutThe download was taking too long and was stopped by the network.Network disconnectedInternet disconnected. Please check your internet connection and try again.Server unavailableServer unavailable.Network errorUnknown network error.No fileThe server could not find the file.Server problemUnknown server error. Please try again, or contact the server administrator.ShutdownThe browser was shut down before the download completed.Starting...$1, $2$1/$2Opening in $1...Opening when completeOpening $1...CancelledRemovedFailed - $1UnconfirmedThis type of file can harm your computer. Do you want to keep $1 anyway?Extensions, apps, and themes can harm your computer. Are you sure you want to continue?This file appears malicious.$1 appears malicious.$1 is not commonly downloaded and could be dangerous.Confirm DownloadThis might hurt. Don't say we didn't warn you...Keep anywayKeepContinueDiscardPauseSearch downloadsSearch results for '$1'ResumeRemove from listCancelRetry downloadShow in folderCancelledRemoved$1 - $2$1 - $2, $3$1 of $2PausedClear allOpen downloads folderOpen when &done&Open&Always open files of this type&Cancel&Pause&Resume&Discard&Keep&Learn more&More information&Show in folderDownload in progressDownloads in progressIncognito download in progressIncognito downloads in progressAn incognito download is currently in progress. Do you want to exit incognito mode and cancel the download?Incognito downloads are currently in progress. Do you want to exit incognito mode and cancel the downloads?Yes, exit incognito modeNoCreate application &shortcuts...Create application shortcuts$1 browserCreate application shortcuts in the following places:DesktopApplications menuStart menuQuick launch barPin to TaskbarCreateThis page was prevented from setting cookies.This page set cookies.Manage cookie blocking...Show cookies and other site data...Images were blocked on this page.Always allow $1 to set cookiesAlways allow $1 to show imagesContinue blocking cookiesContinue blocking imagesManage image blocking...Pop-ups were blocked on this page.The following pop-ups were blocked on this page:Always allow pop-ups from $1Continue blocking pop-upsManage pop-up blocking...Always allow $1 to access your camera and microphoneAsk if $1 wants to access your camera and microphoneAlways block camera and microphone accessContinue blocking camera and microphone accessContinue allowing $1 to access your camera and microphonePop-up blockedJavaScript was blocked on this page.Always allow JavaScript on $1Continue blocking JavaScriptManage JavaScript blocking...The following plug-ins were blocked on this page:Plug-ins were blocked on this page.Always allow plug-ins on $1Always allow these plug-ins on $1Continue blocking plug-insManage plug-in blocking...Run all plug-ins this timeThis page was prerendered.Help me understandWhen you connect to a secure website, the server hosting that site presents your browser with something called a "certificate" to verify its identity. This certificate contains identity information, such as the address of the website, which is verified by a third party that your computer trusts. By checking that the address in the certificate matches the address of the website, it is possible to verify that you are securely communicating with the website you intended, and not a third party (such as an attacker on your network).This is probably not the site you are looking for!You attempted to reach <strong>$1</strong>, but instead you actually reached a server identifying itself as <strong>$2</strong>. This may be caused by a misconfiguration on the server or by something more serious. An attacker on your network could be trying to get you to visit a fake (and potentially harmful) version of <strong>$3</strong>.Server's certificate does not match the URL.The site's security certificate has expired!For a certificate which has not expired, the issuer of that certificate is responsible for maintaining something called a "revocation list". If a certificate is ever compromised, the issuer can revoke it by adding it to the revocation list, and then this certificate will no longer be trusted by your browser. Revocation status is not required to be maintained for expired certificates, so while this certificate used to be valid for the website you're visiting, at this point it is not possible to determine whether the certificate was compromised and subsequently revoked, or whether it remains secure. As such it is impossible to tell whether you're communicating with the legitimate website, or whether the certificate was compromised and is now in the possession of an attacker with whom you are communicating.Server's certificate has expired.The server's security certificate is not yet valid!Certificates have a validity period, much like any identity document (such as a passport) that you may have. The certificate presented to your browser is not yet valid. When a certificate is outside of its validity period, certain information about the status of the certificate (whether it has been revoked and should no longer be trusted) is not required to be maintained. As such, it is not pos