onNetscape Certificate TypeEmail CertificateEmail Certification AuthorityNetscape Certificate Base URLNetscape Certificate Revocation URLNetscape Certification Authority Revocation URLNetscape Certificate Renewal URLNetscape Certification Authority Policy URLNetscape Certificate SSL Server NameNetscape Certificate CommentNetscape Lost Password URLNetscape Certificate Renewal TimeCertificate Subject Directory AttributesCertificate Subject Key IDKey ID: $1Issuer: $1Serial Number: $1Certificate Key UsageCertificate Subject Alternative NameCertificate Issuer Alternative NameCertificate Basic ConstraintsCertificate Name ConstraintsCRL Distribution PointsCertificate PoliciesCertificate Policy MappingsCertificate Policy ConstraintsCertification Authority Key IDExtended Key UsageAuthority Information AccessSigningNon-repudiationKey EnciphermentData EnciphermentKey AgreementCertificate SignerCRL SignerEncipher OnlyIs a Certification AuthorityIs not a Certification AuthorityMaximum number of intermediate CAs: $1unlimitedCertification Practice Statement PointerUser NoticeUnusedKey CompromiseCA CompromiseAffiliation ChangedSupersededCessation of OperationCertificate on HoldOCSP Responder: $1CA Issuers: $1$1: $2$1 ($2)$1:Email AddressDNS NameX.400 AddressX.500 NameEDI Party NameURIIP AddressRegistered OIDMicrosoft Certificate Template NameMicrosoft CA VersionMicrosoft Principal NameMicrosoft Domain GUIDTLS WWW Server AuthenticationTLS WWW Client AuthenticationCode SigningEmail ProtectionTime StampingSigning OCSP ResponsesMicrosoft Individual Code SigningMicrosoft Commercial Code SigningMicrosoft Trust List SigningMicrosoft Time StampingMicrosoft Server Gated CryptographyMicrosoft Encrypting File SystemMicrosoft File RecoveryMicrosoft Windows Hardware Driver VerificationMicrosoft Qualified SubordinationMicrosoft Key RecoveryMicrosoft Document SigningMicrosoft Lifetime SigningMicrosoft Smart Card LogonMicrosoft Key Recovery AgentNetscape International Step-UpCriticalNot CriticalError: Unable to decode extensionCertificate managerYour CertificatesServersAuthoritiesOthersYou have certificates from these organizations that identify you:You have certificates on file that identify these servers:You have certificates on file that identify these certificate authorities:You have certificates on file that do not fit in any of the other categories:Certificate NameCertificate StoreSerial NumberExpires OnView...Import...Export...Export All...Edit...Delete...Delete certificate "$1"?If you delete one of your own certificates, you can no longer use it to identify yourself.Delete server certificate "$1"?If you delete a server certificate, you restore the usual security checks for that server and require it uses a valid certificate.Delete CA certificate "$1"?If you delete a Certification Authority (CA) certificate, your browser will no longer trust any certificates issued by that CA.Delete certificate "$1"?Please enter a password to encrypt this certificate file.The password you choose will be required to restore this file later.  Please record it in a safe location.Please enter the password that was used to encrypt this certificate file.Password:Confirm Password:PKCS #12 FilesPKCS #12 Export ErrorThere was an error while trying to write the file: $1.UntrustedPKCS #12 Import ErrorIncorrect password or corrupt file.Invalid or corrupt file.File uses unsupported features.There was an error while trying to read the file: $1.Incorrect password.Unable to parse file.Unknown error.Not a Certification Authority.Certificate already exists.Certificate Deletion ErrorCertificate authorityEdit trust settings:The certificate "$1" represents a Certification Authority.Trust this certificate for identifying websites.Trust this certificate for identifying email users.Trust this certificate for identifying software makers.Error Setting Certificate TrustDo you want to trust "$1" as a Certification Authority?Certification Authority Import Error$1: $2The file contained one certificate, which was not imported:The file contained multiple certificates, none of which were imported:The file contained multiple certificates, some of which were not imported:Server Certificate Import ErrorThe certificate "$1" was issued by:Add CertificateThe server returned an invalid client certificate. Error $1 ($2).There was an error while trying to store the client certificate. Error $1 ($2).Successfully stored client certificate issued by $1.ViewOKCut it out!"$1" is debugging this tab.The selected folder should contain an empty file with the following name: "$1".Normal ReloadHard ReloadEmpty Cache and Hard ReloadAuthentication RequiredThe server $1 requires a username and password. The server says: $2.The server $1 requires a username and password.User Name:Password:Log InSmile! Take a picture of yourself and set it as your account picture.The camera failed to initialize.Select networkAccept agreementRegisterSign inChoose your account pictureBicycleBokehChessCoffeeDragonflyFrogGanzania FlowerJack Russell TerrierJellyfishKiwiPenguinRainbowfishRecord playerUpside Down$1 of $2PreviousNextClose find barExit full screen($1)The page has hidden the mouse pointer. To restore it, press 'Esc'.End processPurge memoryProcess IDTaskNetworkCPUMemoryPrivate memoryShared memoryProfileGoats teleportedImage cacheScript cacheCSS cacheGPU MemoryFPSSQLite memoryJavaScript memoryInspectActivateStats for nerds$1K$1K ($2K live)N/ABrowserExtension: $1Incognito Extension: $1App: $1Incognito App: $1Tab: $1Background Page: $1Plug-in: $1Plug-in Broker: $1Prerender: $1Unknown plug-inWeb Worker: $1Utility:Native Client module: $1Native Client security managerGPU ProcessNotification: $1Instant: $1Webview: $1PerformanceWarning: You do not have the performance monitoring flag enabled! Data displayed will be limited to any data which were gathered previously.EnableWarning: The data are not being aggregated! This may cause the page to be slow!Time RangeTime ResolutionLast 15 MinutesLast HourLast DayLast WeekLast MonthLast QuarterShift Time WindowAggregation MethodNoneDo not aggregate the data - this may be slow!MedianUse medians, minimizing outlier effect in performance dataMeanWeight all values equally in performance dataEvents to DisplayExtensionsEvents that are related to any extensions that are (or have been) installed in $1InstallsOccurrences when an extension was installedExtension InstalledUninstallsOccurrences when an extension was uninstalledExtension UninstalledUpdatesOccurrences when an extension was updatedExtension UpdatedEnablesOccurrences when an extension was enabledExtension EnabledDisablesOccurrences when an extension was disabledExtension DisabledEvents that are related to the $1 system.UpdatesOccurrences when the version of $1 changed$1 UpdatedExceptionsEvents relating to $1 crashes and failuresRenderer FreezesOccurrences when a tab became unresponsiveRenderer FrozeRenderer CrashesOccurrences when a tab crashed ("$1")Renderer CrashedProcess KillsOccurrences when the OS killed a tab's process ("$1")Process KilledUnclean ExitsOccurrences when $1 did not shut down correctlyUnclean ExitTimeExtension IDExtension NameExtension URLExtension LocationExtension VersionExtension DescriptionPrevious VersionCurrent VersionURLProfile NameMetrics to DisplayCPUMetrics relating to the effect of $1 on the system's CPUCPU UsageThe combined CPU usage of all processes related to $1MemoryMetrics relating to the effect of $1 on the system's memoryPrivate Memory UsageThe combined private memory usage of all processes related to $1Shared Memory UsageThe combined shared memory usage of all processes related to $1TimingMetrics relating to the speed with which $1 performs requested actionsStartupsThe time it takes to fully start $1Test StartupsThe time it takes to fully start $1 in a testing environmentSession RestoresThe time it takes to restore a previous browsing sessionPage LoadsThe time it takes to load a web pageNetworkMetrics related to the network usage of $1Bytes ReadThe number of bytes read across the networkBytesKilobytesMegabytesGigabytesTerabytesMicrosecondsMillisecondsSecondsMinutesHoursDaysWeeksMonthsYearsPercentInstalled theme "$1".UndoThe newest version of the extension "$1" requires more permissions, so it has been disabled.The newest version of the app "$1" requires more permissions, so it has been disabled.Review permissions...$1 requires new permissionsGoogle has flagged $1 as malicious and installation has been prevented.Confirm InstallationConfirm New AppConfirm New ExtensionConfirm New ThemeConfirm RemovalConfirm Re-enableConfirm PermissionsCurrent PermissionsAdd "$1"?Install these extensions?Install these apps?Install these apps and extensions?Remove "$1"?The newest version of "$1" has been disabled because it requires more permissions."$1" has requested additional permissions.$1Confirm ChangesThe extension "$1" has been added.The extension "$1" was automatically removed.The app "$1" has been added.The app "$1" was automatically removed.OKDetailsIt can:It can now:They can:It could:It can:• $1($1)$1 usersView detailsOn your $1 account, it can:On your $1 account, it can now:On your $1 account, it could:Access all data on your computer and the websites you visitAccess your data on all websitesAccess your data on $1Access your data on $1 and $2Access your data on $1, $2, and $3Access your data on $1, $2, and $3 other websitesAccess anything you type.Read and modify your bookmarksRead and modify your browsing historyDetect your physical locationManage your apps, extensions, and themesAccess your tabs and browsing activityAccess the page debugger backendAccess data you copy and pasteAccess all text spoken using synthesized speechManipulate settings that control websites' access to cookies, JavaScript, and plug-insManipulate privacy-related settingsAccess USB devicesAccess Bluetooth on your systemAccess the Bluetooth device "$1".Unknown CompanyUnknown DeviceAccess the USB device "$1 ($2)".Use your microphoneUse your cameraUse your microphone and cameraDownload filesWrite to files that you have opened in the applicationAccess photos, music, and other media from your computer (Read)Access photos, music, and other media to your computer (Read, write, and delete)Use serial devices attached to your computerExchange data with any computer on the local network or internetExchange data with any computer in the domain $1Exchange data with any computer in the domains: $1Exchange data with the computer named $1Exchange data with the computers named: $1Display and manage an icon in the system indicator area.Can't find the absolute path to the directory to pack.Input directory must exist.This can only be added from the $1.Input value for private key must be a valid path.A private key for specified extension already exists. Reuse that key or delete it first.Input value for private key must exist.Pack Extension WarningPack Extension ErrorThere is already a CRX file present with this name.Proceed anywayFailed to read private key.Invalid private key.Yikes! Failed to generate random RSA private key.Failed to export private key.Failed to output private key.Failed to create temporary zip file during packaging.Error while signing extension.Failed to replace crx file. Check to see if the file is in use.Failed to export public key.Attempted to downgrade extension.Attempted to downgrade app.WebGL is not supported.CSS3d is not supported.NPAPI plugins are not supported.This extension is blacklisted.$1 (extension ID "$2") is blocked by the administrator.The administrator of this machine requires $1 to be installed. It cannot be removed or modified.Could not move extension directory into profile.Manifest file is missing or unreadable.Manifest file is invalid.Installation is not enabled.Apps must be served with content-type "$1".Apps must be served from the host they affect.Expected ID "$1", but ID was "$2".Apps, extensions, and user scripts cannot be added from this website.Expected version "$1", but version was "$2".Could not add application because it conflicts with "$1".Localization used, but default_locale wasn't specified in the manifest.Could not load '$1' for theme.Could not load extension icon '$1'.Could not load javascript '$1' for content script.Could not load css '$1' for content script.Could not load file '$1' for content script. It isn't UTF-8 encoded.Could not load '$1' for plugin.Could not load icon '$1' for page action.Could not load icon '$1' for browser action.Could not load background script '$1'.Could not load background page '$1'.Could not load options page '$1'.Can not unpack extension.  To safely unpack an extension, there must be a path to your profile directory that starts with a drive letter and does not contain a junction, mount point, or symlink.  No such path exists for your profile.Package is invalid. Details: '$1'.Package is invalid: '$1'.Could not install package: '$1'This extension includes the key file '$1'. You probably don't want to do that.Could not create directory for unzipping: '$1'Could not unzip extensionIllegal path (absolute or relative with '..'): '$1'Could not decode image: '$1'The following extensions are now installed:The following apps are now installed:The following apps and extensions were added:We were unable to install:Show meThis icon will be visible when the extension can act on the current page.This icon will be visible when the extension can act on the current page. Use this extension by clicking on the icon or by pressing $1.Use this extension by clicking on this icon.Use this extension by clicking on this icon or by pressing $1.To use this extension, type "$1", then TAB, then your command or search.Manage your extensions by clicking Extensions in the Tools menu.Manage your extensions by clicking Extensions in the Window menu.Manage shortcutsSign in to $1 to get this extension, your history, and other Spark settings on all your devices.Infobar ContainerWarningPage ActionDeveloper modeLoad unpacked extension...Pack extension...Update extensions nowBoo... You have no extensions :-(Want to <a target="_blank" href="$1">browse the gallery</a> instead?Drop to install(Crashed)(Unpacked)(Incognito)(Inactive)ID:Loaded from:Inspect views:There were warnings when trying to install this extension:EnableEnabledRemoveAllow in incognitoAllow access to file URLsVisit websiteView in Web StoreReloadLaunchRestartReload (Ctrl+R)OptionsPermissionsActivityShow buttonOptionsDisableHide buttonManage extensions...Inspect popup(This extension is managed and cannot be removed or disabled.)Extensions cannot be modified in managed mode.Get more extensionsSelect the extension directory.Configure commandsKeyboard Shortcuts - Extensions and AppsNo extensions have keyboard shortcuts assigned.Not setType a shortcutDelete shortcutActivate the extensionPack ExtensionPack ExtensionSelect the root directory of the extension to pack. To update an extension, also select the private key file to reuse.Extension root directory:Private key file (optional):Browse...Select extension root directory.Select private key file.Private keyExtension root directory is required.Extension root directory is invalid.Private key file is invalid.Created the following files:

Extension: $1
Key File: $2

Keep your key file in a safe place. You will need it to create new versions of your extension.Created the extension:

$1Install FailureAddRemoveRe-enableAllowDenyChrome Web StoreWeb StoreShow DetailsHide DetailsExtension ActivityAPI CallBlocked API CallContent ScriptAPI Event$1 is running on this page.Last updated:Extension errorWarning:This extension is slowing down $1. You should disable it to restore $1's performance.This extension failed to modify a network request because the modification conflicted with another extension.This extension failed to redirect a network request to $1 because another extension ($2) redirected it to $3.This extension failed to modify the request header "$1" of a network request because the modification conflicted with another extension ($2).This extension failed to modify the response header "$1" of a network request because the modification conflicted with another extension ($2).This extension failed to provide credentials to a network request because another extension ($1) provided different credentials.New extension added ($1)New app added ($1)New theme added ($1)"$1" addedAnother program on your computer added an extension that may change the way Spark works.Another program on your computer added an app that may change the way Spark works.Another program on your computer added a theme that may change the way Spark works.Enable extensionEnable appEnable themeRemove from SparkApp LauncherSwitch userSign in with your Google Account to allow apps to synchronize settings and provide other customized services.Allow apps to ask to become default handlers for protocols (recommended)Do not allow any app to handle protocolsAllow all apps to show desktop notificationsDo not allow any app to show desktop notificationsAsk me when an app wants to show desktop notifications (recommended)Plug-insDetailsNo plug-ins installed.(Disabled)(Disabled by enterprise policy)(Enabled by enterprise policy)(Managed by enterprise policy)Version:Description:Location:Type:MIME types:MIME typeDescriptionFile extensionsDisableEnableAlways allowedDownload Critical Security UpdateName:No plugins are installedNPAPIPPAPI (in-process)PPAPI (out-of-process)PPAPI (unsandboxed)Request succeededInvalid request or request parametersNetwork errorTemporary server errorHTTP errorFailed to decode responseManagement not supportedMissing device recordInvalid device management tokenActivation is pending on the serverDevice serial number is invalidConflicting device identifierLicenses exhaustedPolicy not foundUnknown errorValidation successfulBad signatureError code present in the policy responseError parsing policyWrong policy typeBad policy timestampReturned policy token doesn't match current tokenWrong policy subjectError parsing policy settingsUnknown errorPolicy cache OKFailed to load policy settingsFailed to store policy settingsPolicy parse errorSerialization errorValidation error: $1.Backing store in bad stateUnknown errorExpected $1 value.Value is out of range $1.Value doesn't match format.Ignored because default search is disabled by policy.Must be specified.Key "$1": $2List entry "$1": $2Invalid search URL.Invalid proxy mode.Use of a proxy is disabled but an explicit proxy configuration is specified.Proxy is set to auto configured.Proxy configuration is set to use a .pac script URL, not fixed proxy servers.Proxy is set to use fixed proxy servers, not a .pac script URL.System proxy settings are set to be used but an explicit proxy configuration is also specified.Both fixed proxy servers and a .pac script URL are specified.Neither fixed proxy servers nor a .pac script URL are specified.Ignored because it was overridden by $1.This policy has been deprecated.This value is deprecated for this policy.Network configuration failed to be parsed.The network configuration doesn't comply to the ONC standard. Parts of the configuration may not be imported.The network configuration is invalid and couldn't be imported.OKNot set.Unknown policy.PoliciesFilter policies by nameReload policiesStatusDevice policiesUser policiesEnrollment domain:User:Client ID:Last fetched:NeverFetch interval:Status:Show policies with no value setNo policies setApplies toLevelPolicy namePolicy valueStatusShow valueHide valueCurrent userMachineRecommendedMandatoryCareful, these experiments may biteExperimentsWARNINGThese experimental features may change, break, or disappear at any time. We make absolutely no guarantees about what may happen if you turn one of these experiments on, and your browser may even spontaneously combust. Jokes aside, your browser may delete all your data, or your security and privacy could be compromised in unexpected ways. Any experiments you enable will be enabled for all users of this browser. Please proceed with caution.Aww, it looks like there are currently no experiments available.Sorry, this experiment is not available on your platform.Relaunch NowDisableEnableTab OverviewSwipe down with three fingers on your trackpad while holding the option key to see an overview of all your tabs. Click on a thumbnail to select it. Works great in fullscreen mode.Stacked TabsTabs never shrink, instead they stack on top of each other when there is not enough space.Instant Autocomplete ImmediatelyWhether the search provider suggestion should be autocompleted immediately when instant is enabled.Native ClientEnable Native Client for all web applications, even those that were not installed from the Chrome Web Store.Native Client hardware exception handlingEnable support for Native Client hardware exception handling.Native Client GDB-based debuggingEnable GDB debug stub. This will stop a Native Client application on startup and wait for nacl-gdb (from the NaCl SDK) to attach to it.Restrict Native Client GDB-based debugging by patternRestricts Native Client application GDB-based debugging by URL of manifest file. Native Client GDB-based debugging must be enabled for this option to work.Debug only if manifest URL ends with debug.nmfDebug everything except secure shellPortable Native Client.Enable support for Portable Native Client.New Downloads UIDisables the download shelf. Will show the new downloads UI as it is implemented.Save Page as MHTMLDisables saving pages as HTML-only or HTML Complete; enables saving pages only as MHTML: a single text file containing HTML and all sub-resources.XSS AuditorEnables WebKit's XSS Auditor (cross-site scripting protection). This feature aims to protect you from certain attacks of malicious websites. It improves your security, but it might not be compatible with all websites.Cloud Print ConnectorEnables a background service that connects the Google Cloud Print service to any printers installed on this computer. Once this lab is enabled, you can turn the Google Cloud Print Connector on by logging in with your Google account in the Under the Hood section of Settings.Print rasterRasterise page before printing. Slower, but may help to resolve issues with some printersCRX-less Web AppsEnables support for installing Chrome apps that are deployed using a manifest file on a webpage, rather than by packaging the manifest and icons into a crx file.Touch Optimized UIEnables experimental layout refinements to improve user experience with touch screens.Enable touch eventsForce touchscreen support to always be enabled or disabled, or to be enabled when a touchscreen is detected on startup (Automatic, the default).Disable touch adjustment.Disables touch adjustment support.  Touch adjustment is the process of refining the position of a touch gesture in order to compensate for touches having poor resolution compared to a mouse.Enable Tab Capture APIEnables experimental tab capture API to generate video streams of tab content.Enable background loader component for hosted applicationsEnable background loader component for hosted applications.Enable bezel touch actionsEnable bezel touch actions.Enable screensaver extensions.Enable screensaver extensions.Check for known conflicts with 3rd party modules.Enables a background check that warns you when a software incompatibility is detected (ie. 3rd party modules that crash the browser).GPU Accelerated CompositingEnables 3D CSS and higher performance compositing of webpages using Graphics Processor Unit (GPU) hardware.Composited render layer bordersRenders a border around composited Render Layers to help debug and study layer compositing.GPU Accelerated PaintingEnable GPU accelerated painting of page contents when compositing is enabled.FPS counterShows a page's actual frame rate, in frames per second, when hardware acceleration is active.GPU Accelerated SVG FiltersUse the GPU to accelerate rendering of SVG filters.Composite to TextureEnables compositing to offscreen texture instead of directly to display.Debugging keyboard shortcutsEnables additional keyboard shortcuts that are useful for debugging Spark.GPU compositing on all pagesUses GPU accelerated compositing on all pages, not just those that include GPU-accelerated layers.Do SHOW Presents with GDI.Speculative fix for http://crbug.com/169848FirstAllForce high DPI modeOverrides the device display density to force the use of high DPI mode and assets.Override software rendering listOverrides the built-in software rendering list and enables GPU-acceleration on unsupported system configurations.Disable GPU VSyncDisables synchronization with the display's vertical refresh rate when GPU rendering. This allows frame rates to exceed
        60 hertz. While useful for benchmarking purposes, this also results in visual tearing during rapid screen updates.Threaded compositingUses a secondary thread to perform web page compositing. This allows smooth scrolling, even when the main thread is unresponsive.Accelerated overflow scrollWhen possible, puts the scrolling contents of an overflow scrolling element onto a composited layer for faster scrolling.Disable accelerated 2D canvasDisables the use of the GPU to perform 2d canvas rendering and instead uses software rendering.Disable deferred 2D canvasDisables the deferral of 2d canvas rendering, causing draw operations to be completed immediately, before running the next javascript command.Disable accelerated CSS animationsWhen threaded compositing is enabled, accelerated CSS animations run on the compositing thread. However, there may be performance gains running with accelerated CSS animations, even without the compositor thread.WebGLEnables canvas elements to use 3D graphics via the WebGL API.Experimental Extension APIsEnables experimental extension APIs. Note that the extension gallery doesn't allow you to upload extensions that use experimental APIs.Action boxEnable or disable the "Action Box" experimental toolbar UI.Extensions in the Action boxEnables to show "Extensions the Action Box" (Action box has to be enabled).Script badgesShows extension "script badges" in the location bar rather than page actions.Script BubbleEnable or disable the "Script Bubble" experimental toolbar UI.New Apps Install BubbleWhen installing an app, always show a bubble pointing at the new tab page button on the tabstrip instead of opening a new tab page.Click to playEnables a "click to play" option in the plug-in content settings.Disable hyperlink auditingDisable sending hyperlink auditing pings.Experimental location featuresEnables experimental extensions to the geolocation feature to use operating system location APIs (where available).Experimental static ip configurationEnables static ip configuration. May not work.Add grouping to tab context menuAdds items to the tab context menu for grouping tabs.VPN supportShow Private networks in the Network menu to enable conencting to a VPN.NTP Suggestions pageAdd 'Suggestions' card to the new tab page, which suggests the pages to be opened.Enable Instant extended APIEnable the Instant extended API.Gesture Tap HighlightingEnable the experimental gesture tap highlight implementation.Smooth ScrollingEnable the experimental smooth scrolling implementation.Enable auto-loginWhen enabled, visiting a Google account login page will trigger an infobar allowing easy sign in with the Google account connected to the profile.
        Auto-login is always disabled if the profile is not connected to an account, regardless of this flag.Show Autofill predictionsAnnotates web forms with Autofill field type predictions as placeholder text.Enable new Autofill UIEnable the browser process-based implementation of the Autofill UI, as opposed to the renderer process-based one.Enable new Autofill heuristicsEnable new Autofill heuristics.  This primarily covers detection of additional field types, such as credit card type.Enable interactive autocompleteEnable an interactive autocomplete UI that can be invoked by calling HTMLFormElement#requestAutocomplete.Enable touch initiated drag and dropTouch drag and drop can be initiated through long press on a draggable element.Enable experimental form fillingEnable experimental form filling. Enables a collection of experimental features that make form filling easier.Enable overscroll history navigationEnables experimental history navigation in response to horizontal overscroll.Enable syncing search enginesEnable search engines in the sync settings. This allows syncing your custom search engines to other clients.Enable syncing open tabsEnable open tabs in the sync settings. This allows syncing your open tabs to other clients.Enable tab favicon sync.Enable syncing the favicons of open tabs as part of Open Tab sync.Disable syncing app notificationsDisable app notifications in the sync settings. This turns off syncing notifications received from your apps to other clients.Enable sync keystore encryption.Switch to sync's new server supported encryption schema. Warning: this will modify your sync data, possibly making it unreadable to other clients.Enable syncing Omnibox HistoryEnable Omnibox History in the sync settings. This allows syncing your typed URL history to other clients to assist in omnibox auto-completion.Use new scoring in HistoryQuickProviderIn omnibox autocomplete, use the new scoring function for ranking matches coming from HistoryQuickProvider.AutomaticNew ScoringOld ScoringReorder results for inlining in HistoryQuickProviderIn omnibox autocomplete, reorder suggestions in HistoryQuickProvider to make an inlineable one appear first.AutomaticReorderDon't ReorderInline HistoryQuickProvider suggestionsIn omnibox autocomplete, allow inlining of matches coming from the HistoryQuickProvider.AutomaticAllowedProhibitedSend additional Autofill feedbackHelp improve Autofill.  With this enabled, Spark will occasionally prompt you to send additional feedback to the Autofill team.Enable PanelsEnable Panel windows that open outside of the browser frame. Attempts to open a Panel will open a popup instead if not enabled. Panels are always enabled on the dev and canary channels.Enable Panel StackingEnabling this option allows detached panels to be stacked together.Enable WebGLEnabling this option allows web applications to access the WebGL API.Disable WebGLEnabling this option prevents web applications from accessing the WebGL API.Enable WebRTCEnabling this option allows web applications to access the WebRTC API.Fixed position elements create stacking contexts.Enabling this option makes all fixed position elements create new CSS stacking contexts.Compositing for fixed position elements.Enabling this option will make fixed position elements have their own composited layers. Note that fixed position elements must also create stacking contexts for this to work.Enabled only for high-DPI displaysEnable deferred image decoding.Defer image decoding operations in WebKit until painting.HTTP PipeliningEnable experimental pipelining of HTTP requests.Enable SPDY/3Enable experimental SPDY/3.Built-in Asynchronous DNSEnable experimental asynchronous DNS client.Enable extension alertsEnable various alerts about changes in extension state.Disable Media Source API on <video> elements.Disable experimental Media Source API on the video elements. This API allows JavaScript to send media data directly to a video element.Disable Encrypted Media Extensions on <video> elements.Disable experimental Encrypted Media Extensions on the video elements.Enable Opus playback in <video> elements.Enable experimental Opus playback in the video element.Enable VP9 playback in <video> elements.Enable experimental VP9 playback in the video element.Translucent windowsEnable translucent window frames.Automatic window placement.Per application sorting in the launcher.Enable the per application sorting mode of the launcher.Disable automatic window placement for one and two browser / app windows.Throttle the rate of window resize.Disable throttling the rate of window resize. We throttle the resize for less perceived latency.Web Audio InputEnables live audio input using getUserMedia() and the Web Audio API.Enable advanced gesturesEnables advanced gestures (e.g. 4-finger pinch to minimize window etc.).Enable tab scrubbingEnables tab switching via 3 finger horizontal scroll.Enable workspace scrubbingEnables workspace switching via 3 finger vertical scroll.Immersive modeAdds an "immersive mode" for browser windows that gives more space to web content. Activate immersive mode by maximizing a window then clicking on the button in the top right corner.Enable memory monitorEnables visual memory monitor in status area.Enable new network handlers in the status areaEnables the new network handlers which handle Shill communication without using NetworkLibrary for the status area.Enable New Network State HandlerEnables the new Network State Handler which handles Shill communication in the Status Area without using NetworkLibrary.Enable locally managed usersEnables support for user profiles that are managed by another user and can have restrictions applied.AutomaticDefaultEnabledDisabledPer-tile PaintingEnable per-tile painting of page contents when compositing is enabled.Enable Experimental JavaScriptEnable web pages to use experimental JavaScript features.Enable Tab Browser DraggingEnable creating a browser window when dragging tabs.Enable Download ResumptionAllow downloads that have been interrupted to be continued or restarted, using the Resume context menu item.Disable Better session restoreDisables the Better session restore features which restore more session state (e.g., session cookies) after restarts and crashes.Disable 3D software rasterizerDon't fall back to a 3D software rasterizer when the GPU cannot be used.Enable experimental WebKit features.Enable experimental WebKit features that are in development.Enable CSS Shaders.Enable filter effects on DOM elements using custom GLSL shaders. More info at https://dvcs.w3.org/hg/FXTF/raw-file/tip/filters/index.html#feCustomElement.NTP App Install HintShows a + widget to install additional apps on apps pane of the NTP.Enable extension activity UIEnable experimental UI that shows a log of extension activity.Disable NTP 'Other devices' menu.Disable the new tab page menu for accessing tabs on other devices.Disable Uber Tray.Disables the uber tray for ash. Switches to using the old status view.Enable Oak.Enables the Oak tree viewer in ash. Allows inspection of window, layer and view hierarchies and their properties. Press Ctrl+Shift+F1 to access.Enable Developer Tools experiments.Enable Developer Tools experiments. Use Settings panel in Developer Tools to toggle individual experiments.Enable Automatic Spelling CorrectionTurn on autocorrection of text while typing. Synchronous spellchecking is not compatible with this feature.Don't discard tabs.Turns off tab discarding, a feature that discards infrequently used tabs under low memory conditions.Show launcher alignment menu.Enables a menu that allows changing the side the launcher is aligned to.Show HUD for touch pointsEnables a heads-up display at the top-left corner of the screen that lists information about the touch-points on the screen.NaCl Socket API.Allows applications to use NaCl Socket API. Use only to test NaCl plugins.Disable Ash notifications.Disables ash status tray notifications and enables desktop system notifications.Enable pinch scale.Enables experimental support for scale using pinch.Enable apps only search for app list.Shows only apps in app list search.Enable New Dialog Style.Enables a new visual style on certain dialogs.Enable Views Textfield.Enables an experimental textfield for application UI; does not affect web content.Enable contacts integration.Enables downloading Google contacts and displaying them in the App List.Disable new checkbox style.Enable full history sync.If tab sync is enabled, this feature allows you to see and delete history entries from your synced devices at spark://history.Enable RTCDataChannel.Enable experimental RTCDataChannel for peer-to-peer data communications.Disables new appearance and sizing behavior for checkboxes and radio buttons.Disable non full screen mouse lock.Disable hardware-accelerated video decode.Disables hardware-accelerated video decode where available.Enable webpage text sub-pixel positioning.Allows text glyphs on web pages to have X positions which aren't snapped to the pixel grid.Enable switching between mobile carriers.Allows the user to switch between mobile carriers from the UI. Warning: The Sprint carrier will ONLY work for users with an existing Sprint plan.Enables the request tablet site option in the settings menu.Allows the user to request tablet site. Web content is often optimized for tablet devices. When this option is selected the user agent string is changed to indicate a tablet device. Web content optimized for tablets is received there after for the current tab.Enable debugging for packed apps.Enables debugging context menu options such as Inspect Element for packed applications.Enable password generation.Allow the user to have Spark generate passwords when it detects account creation pages.Enable crashing on GPU hang.Crash the GPU process whenever Spark detects that it has hung.Enable performance monitoringEnable passive gathering of performance-related metrics and events and provide the option to view this data in a graphical fashion. To view data, visit spark://performance.Enable Rich NotificationsEnable rich templated notifications. Both HTML5 notifications and app notifications will be shown through new Notification Center.Enable screen capture support in getUserMedia().Allow web pages to request access to the screen contents via the getUserMedia() API.Impl-side paintingIf enabled, painting is done on a separate thread instead of the main thread.CrashesCrashes ($1)Crash ID $1Occurred $1File bugYou have no recently reported crashes.  Crashes that occurred when crash reporting was disabled will not appear here.Crash reporting is disabled.Custom spelling dictionaryAdd a new wordSearch dictionaryNo matches were found.With Instant enabled and if supported by your default search engine, search results appear instantly as you type queries in the omnibox, and in-line predictions help guide your search.

        Because search results are requested even while you're typing your query, your default search engine may be logging these as search queries.Set which search engine is used when searching from the omnibox.http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?answer=95440&hl=enAllow your search engine to provide Instant results (omnibox input may be <a target="_blank" href="$1">logged</a>)Enable Instant for faster searching (omnibox input may be logged)Enable Instant for faster searchingOmnibox input may be loggedModules ($1) - No conflicts detectedModules ($1) - Known conflicts: $2, suspected: $3This page lists all modules loaded into the main process and modules registered to load at a later point.We are currently investigating this issue.If you are experiencing frequent problems, you could try the following to resolve the issue with this module:UninstallingUpdatingDisabling/Unable to detect any modules loaded.SoftwareSigned byLocationVersionHelp tipLoading...Not loaded yethttp://www.google.com/support/chrome/bin/answer.py?answer=1093113&topic=21605&hl=en&n=$1&l=$2&d=$3&s=$4Click to run $1.Hide this plug-inUpdate plug-in...This plug-in only works on the desktop.$1 is not allowed.This app is not currently supported on this device but the Spark gnomes are hard at work to make it work soon.$1 is out of date.$1 needs your permission to run.This plug-in is not supported.No plug-in available to display this content.Looking for plug-in...Downloading $1...There was an error ($1) while downloading the plug-in.$1 download failed.$1 download was cancelled.When $1 has finished installing, reload the page to activate it.When $1 has finished updating, reload the page to activate it.$1 is required to display this content.Install $1Are you sure you want to install $1? You should only install plug-ins that you trust.Install$1 has been disabled. To re-enable it, please go to spark://plugins.RestoreYou are using an unsupported command-line flag: $1. Stability and security will suffer.$1 on $2 wants to access your computer.AllowDenyAn unsandboxed plug-in was prevented from running on this page.An unsandboxed plug-in was allowed to run running on this page.Always allow unsandboxed plug-ins on $1Continue blocking unsandboxed plug-insContinue allowing unsandboxed plug-insNever allow unsandboxed plug-ins on $1Manage unsandboxed plug-in blocking...This page includes script from unauthenticated sources.Load unsafe scriptDon't load (recommended)Loading...About FlashLoading...About NaClThis page uses a Native Client app that doesn't work on your computer.About VersionApplicationOfficial BuildDeveloper BuildOSUser AgentCommand LineBuild DateExecutable PathProfile PathNo such file or directoryVariationsBuild IDJavaScript AlertJavaScriptThe page at $1 says:The page at $1 says:Prevent this page from creating additional dialogs.An error occurred while checking for updates: $1Update check failed to start (error code $1).Confirm NavigationAre you sure you want to leave this page?Leave this PageStay on this PageConfirm ReloadAre you sure you want to reload this page?Reload this PageDon't ReloadAdd PageAddURL:PageURLRecently visited sitesCopy URLPa&ste and goPa&ste and searchPress $1 to search $2Press $1 to send commands to $2Search $1:$1 SearchAlways on topClick to go back, hold to see historyPress enter to go back, context menu key to see historyClick to go forward, hold to see historyPress enter to go forward, context menu key to see historyOpen the home pageToggle immersive modeReload this pageReload this page, hold to see more optionsStop loading this pageView extensions interacting with pageBookmark this pageEdit bookmark for this pageCloseView site informationNew tabActionsZoom: $1%Reset to defaultBookmark this pageEdit bookmarkSend tab to deviceFind places to shareExtensions interacting with this page:$1 (Incognito)$1 (Update is available)BackForwardHomeReloadAddress and search barScript BubbleBookmarkZoomSpark To MobileOpen PDF in ReaderFindPreviousNextTabstripBookmarksMenu containing hidden bookmarksSeparatorExtensionsBrowser ActionMenu containing hidden extensionsNew TabImmersive ModeMinimizeMaximizeRestoreCloseWeb ContentsActionsUnknownPlug-in UnresponsiveThe following plug-in is unresponsive: $1
Would you like to stop it?Page(s) UnresponsiveThe following page(s) have become unresponsive. You can wait for them to become responsive or kill them.WaitKill pagesA plug-in ($1) isn't responding.Stop plug-inPasswordsSaved passwordsNever savedSearch passwordsSiteUsernameRemoveAre you sure you want to remove all passwords?Remove all passwordsShowHideYour saved passwords will appear here.Sites which never save passwords will appear here.Remove allYesNoSave passwordNever for this siteImport bookmarks and settingsFrom:Microsoft Internet ExplorerMozilla FirefoxIceweaselGoogle ToolbarSafariSelect items to import:Browsing historyFavorites/BookmarksSaved passwordsSearch enginesLoading...Success!ImportIn order to import Toolbar bookmarks into Spark, you must be signed in to your Google account.  Please sign in and try to import again.No supported browser foundImportingFavorites/BookmarksSearch settingsSaved passwordsBrowsing historyCookiesStop importHold $1 to Quit.Warn Before Quitting ($1)Close Firefox Before ImportingContinueSkip ImportWhoops. Let's fix that.FeedbackInclude this URL:Include this email:Tell us what is happening. (required)Include this screenshot:Include a saved screenshot:Send a current page screen shotSend a saved screen shotSend system information(Choose a different screenshot)(Go back to original screenshot)The attached file is uploaded to Google servers for debugging.<br>
        Note: You can attach one file per feedback report (3 MB limit)Attach this file:Reading file..Selected file is too big.Your Spark and Operating system version will be submitted in addition
        to any information you choose to include above. This feedback is used to
        diagnose problems and help improve Spark. Any personal information you
        submit, whether explicitly or incidentally will be protected in
        accordance with our privacy policies.<strong> By submitting this feedback, you agree that Baidu may use feedback
        that you provide to improve any Baidu product or service. Send feedback
        will have the chance to get reward up to $150.
        </strong>Send last active tab screen shotDo not send a screen shotPlease tell us what is happening before sending the feedback.You can select saved screenshots from here. Currently there are no screenshots available. You can press Ctrl + the "Window Switch" key together to take a screenshot. The last three screenshots that you have taken will appear here.Send feedbackClear browsing dataPsst! Incognito mode ($1) may come in handy next time.Obliterate the following items from:Clear browsing historyClear download historyEmpty the cacheDelete cookies and other site dataDelete cookies and other site and plug-in dataClear saved passwordsClear saved Autofill form dataClear data from hosted appsDeauthorize content licensesClear browsing dataAdobe Flash Player storage settings...the past hourthe past daythe past weekthe last 4 weeksthe beginning of timeClearing...Managed User SettingsInstalled and enabled content packs:Get Content PacksWhen a managed user tries to access a site that is not in any content pack:AllowWarnBlockAdvanced settingsEnable Google's SafeSearchDisable signing into SparkDisable incognito windows and deleting historyUse a passphrase to leave managed modeSet passphraseSet a passphraseSet a passphrase to access managed user settings and other profiles.Enter a passphrase:Confirm the passphrase:The passphrases do not match.SaveSad RobotSorry, you're not allowed to access the following page:Go backContent PacksCustodians can also allow this site.PreviewContent settingsCookiesCookie and site data exceptionsAllow local data to be set (recommended)Keep local data only until I quit my browserBlock sites from setting any dataExceptions...Block third-party cookies and site dataWeb IntentsAllow Web Intents to enable me to connect my applications.MediaMedia exceptionsDo not allow sites to access my camera and microphoneAsk me when a site requires access to my camera and microphone (recommended)Do not allow sites to access my microphoneAsk me when a site requires access to my microphone (recommended)Do not allow sites to access my cameraAsk me when a site requires access to my camera (recommended)Access to your microphone is controlled by your administrator.Access to your camera is controlled by your administrator.Microphone:Camera:Adobe Flash Player camera and microphone settings are different.Adobe Flash Player camera and microphone exceptions are different.ChangeMedia galleriesMedia galleriesManage galleriesAdd...AudioVideoReloadClear cookies and other site data when I close my browserClear cookies and other site and plug-in data when I close my browserImagesImage exceptionsShow all images (recommended)Do not show any imagesPop-upsPop-up exceptionsPop-up settings:Allow all sites to show pop-upsDo not allow any site to show pop-ups (recommended)Plug-insPlug-in exceptionsWhen I encounter plug-ins on a site:Run automatically (recommended)Click to playBlock allDisable individual plug-ins...JavaScriptJavaScript exceptionsAllow all sites to run JavaScript (recommended)Do not allow any site to run JavaScriptHandlersAllow sites to ask to become default handlers for protocols (recommended)Do not allow any site to handle protocolsThis site was prevented from registering a custom URL handler.Manage handler settings...TypeSiteremove this site(none)Active protocol handlersIgnored protocol handlersProtocol handlersLocationGeolocation exceptionsAllow all sites to track my physical locationAsk me when a site tries to track my physical location (recommended)Do not allow any site to track my physical locationLocation exceptionsSet by app:NotificationsNotifications exceptionsSettings...Allow all sites to show desktop notificationsDo not allow any site to show desktop notificationsAsk me when a site wants to show desktop notifications (recommended)FullscreenFullscreen exceptionsSiteHostname patternBehaviorAdd...Edit...RemoveRemove allAllowAskClear on exitBlockExceptions below only apply to the current incognito session.[*.]example.comAdd a new hostname patternembedded on $1embedded on any other siteMouse cursorMouse cursor exceptionsAllow all sites to disable the mouse cursorAsk me when a site tries to disable the mouse cursor (recommended)Do not allow any site to disable the mouse cursorUnsandboxed plug-in accessAllow all sites to use a plug-in to access my computerDo not allow any sites to use a plug-in to access my computerAsk me when a site wants to use a plug-in to access my computer (recommended)Manage exceptions...All cookies and site data...Manage handlers...Manage intents...Checking for updates...Installing new version...Update failed (error: $1)Updates are disabled by the administratorReport an issueUntitled DocumentNo printer found. Please install a printer.Print FailedSomething went wrong when trying to print.  Please check your printer and try again.Set up or manage printers in $1.Open $1Set up $1Access and share your printers online with $1<span jscontent="googleCloudPrint"></span> is built on the idea that printing can be more intuitive, accessible, and useful. Using <span jscontent="googleCloudPrint"></span> you can make your printers available to you from any <span jscontent="googleCloudPrint"></span> enabled web or mobile app.Print from anywhereAccess your printers from any computer or smart phone. <a href="#" onclick="cloudprint.learnMore()">Learn more</a>Manage your printerReview your print jobs and printer status online.Shared accessShare and control access to your printers with any Google account.$1 has registered the printers on this machine with <b>$2</b>.  You can now print to your printers from any $1 enabled web or mobile app!Print a Test PageAn error occurred while retrieving printer capabilities for printer $1. This printer could not be registered with $2.Received a notification for an unknown printer.The $1 connector requires that the Microsoft XML Paper Specification Essentials Pack be installed.There was a problem listing printers. Some of your printers may not have registered successfully with $1.The $1 connector process has crashed. Restart?PrintGoogle Cloud PrintLoading previewPrint preview failed.The selected printer is not available or not installed correctly.  Check your printer or try selecting another printer.PrintSavePrinting...Saving to PDF in progressCancelAllDestinationBlack and whiteCollateColorLandscapePortraitTwo-sidedPagesLayoutCopiese.g. 1-5, 8, 11-13page range text boxpage range radio buttonSave as PDFLoading $1Total: $1 $2 ($3 $4)Total: $1 $2sheets of papersheet of paperpagepagesPrint using system dialog... $1Print using $1 dialog... $2Print using $1 dialog...Invalid page range, use $1Use a number to indicate how many copies to print (1 or more).IncrementDecrementPrint Specific PagesOptionsHeaders and footersFit to pageBackground colors and imagesSelection onlyMarginsDefaultNoneCustomMinimumTop marginBottom marginLeft marginRight marginPrint using system dialog…Select a destinationShowing destinations for $1Print to Google Docs and other cloud destinations. $1Sign in$2 to print to Google Cloud Print.Search destinationsNo destinations foundShow All...($1 total)Recent DestinationsLocal DestinationsGoogle Cloud PrintManage...Setup...Change...Offline for more than a yearOffline for more than a monthOffline for more than a weekCurrently offlineBy printing to FedEx Office, you accept their $1terms of use$2.I agreeAdd PrintersYou can add printers to your computer by clicking the "Add a printer"
        button below. If you have no printers to add, you'll still be able to save
        a PDF or save to Google Drive.Adding your printers to Google Cloud Print allows you to print from
        anywhere, to anywhere. Share your printers with whoever you choose and
        print to them from Chrome, your phone, tablet, PC, or any other
        web-connected device. $1Learn more$2Add a printerNot nowWaiting for $1...extension $1Waiting for cache...Waiting for AppCache...Waiting for proxy tunnel...Resolving proxy...Resolving host in proxy script...Downloading proxy script...Resolving host...Connecting...Establishing secure connection...Sending request...Uploading ($1%)...Waiting for $1...New tabReloadDuplicateClose tabClose tabsClose other tabsClose tabs to the rightPin tabPin tabsUnpin tabUnpin tabsBookmark all tabs...Use side tabsSelect by domainSelect by openerFor quick access, place your bookmarks here on the bookmarks bar.Imported From IEImported From FirefoxImported From SafariImported From Google ToolbarImportedName:URL:New folder&New folderEdit BookmarkThis folder contains $1 bookmarks. Are you sure you want to delete it?Mobile bookmarksOther bookmarksBookmarks barNew folderEdit folder nameNew folderBookmark Added!BookmarkEdit...RemoveName:Folder:Choose another folder...Like this site? Click here to bookmark it!DismissSend this page to $1.Send this page to:Also send a copy for offline viewing ($1)generating...An error occurred while generating the offline copySendSendingSending.Sending..Sending...Sent!ErrorAn error occurred while sending the pageSend this page to your mobile deviceReloadOpen browser window&Open in new tabOpen in &new windowOpen in &incognito windowAdd pa&ge...Add &folder...&Open all bookmarksOpen all bookmarks in &new windowOpen all bookmarks in &incognito window&DeleteName:&Edit...&Rename...Are you sure you want to open $1 tabs?Here are some suggestions:<a jsvalues="href:reloadUrl">Reload</a> this webpage later.Disable your extensions and then <a jsvalues="href:reloadUrl">reload</a> this webpage.Go to the home page of the site:Check your Internet connection. Restart any router, modem, or other
        network devices you may be using.Check your DNS settings. Contact your network administrator if you're
        not sure what this means.Add
        <span jscontent="productName"></span>
        as a permitted program in your firewall's or antivirus software's settings. If it is
        already a permitted program, try deleting it from the list of permitted programs
        and adding it again.If you use a proxy server, check your proxy settings or contact your
          network administrator to make sure the proxy server is working. If you
          don't believe you should be using a proxy server, adjust your proxy
          settings:
          $1<a jsvalues="href:learnMoreUrl">Learn more</a> about this problem.$1 is not availableAccess to $1 denied.$1 is not found$1 failed to load$1 was blockedThis webpage is not availableUnable to access the networkUnable to connect to the proxy serverUnable to connect to the InternetCache missCache read errorNetwork access suspendedThis webpage is not foundThis webpage has a redirect loopNo data receivedDuplicate headers received from serverServer has a weak ephemeral Diffie-Hellman public keyThis webpage was blocked by an extensionThe webpage at <strong jscontent="failedUrl"></strong> might be temporarily down or it may have moved permanently to a new web address.<span jscontent="productName"></span>
        could not load the webpage because
        <strong jscontent="hostName"></strong>
        took too long to respond.  The website may be down, or you may be
        experiencing issues with your Internet connection.The connection to
        <strong jscontent="hostName"></strong>
        was interrupted.The connection to
        <strong jscontent="hostName"></strong>
        was interrupted by a change in the network connection.<span jscontent="productName"></span>'s
        connection attempt to
        <strong jscontent="hostName"></strong>
        was rejected.  The website may be down, or your network may not be
        properly configured.The server at
        <strong jscontent="hostName"></strong>
        can't be found, because the DNS lookup failed.  DNS is the network
        service that translates a website's name to its Internet address.  This
        error is most often caused by having no connection to the Internet or a
        misconfigured network.  It can also be caused by an unresponsive DNS
        server or a firewall preventing
        <span jscontent="productName"></span>
        from accessing the network.<span jscontent="productName"></span>
        cannot reach the website.  This is typically caused by network issues,
        but can also be the result of a misconfigured firewall or proxy server.The file at <strong jscontent="failedUrl"></strong> is not readable.  It may have been removed, moved, or file permissions may be preventing access.<span jscontent="productName"></span>
          is having trouble accessing the network.
          <br /><br />
          This may be because your firewall or antivirus software wrongly thinks
          <span jscontent="productName"></span>
          is an intruder on your computer and is blocking it from connecting to the Internet.A proxy server is a server that acts as an intermediary between your computer and other servers.  Right now, your system is configured to use a proxy, but
          <span jscontent="productName"></span>
          can't connect to it.<span jscontent="productName"></span>
          can't display the webpage because your computer isn't connected to the Internet.$1
          <br /><br />
          You can try to diagnose the problem by taking the following steps:
          <br /><br />
          $2Go to
          <strong>
          Start > Control Panel > Network and Internet > Network and Sharing Center > Troubleshoot Problems (at the bottom) > Internet Connections.
          </strong>Go to
          <strong>
          Start > Control Panel > Network Connections > New Connection Wizard
          </strong>
          to test your connection.Click
          <strong>Start</strong>,
          click
          <strong>Run</strong>,
          type
          <strong>%windir%\network diagnostic\xpnetdiag.exe</strong>,
          and then click
          <strong>OK</strong>.The webpage was not found in the cache.  Certain resources
        can only be safely loaded from the cache, such as pages generated
        from submitted data.
        <br /><br />
        This error can also be caused by cache corruption due to
        an improper shutdown.
        <br /><br />
        If the problem persists, try clearing the cache.To speed up webpages,
        <span jscontent="productName"></span>
        temporarily saves downloaded files to disk. When
        <span jscontent="productName"></span>
        is not shut down properly, these files can become corrupted, resulting
        in this error.  Reloading the page should resolve this issue, and
        shutting down properly should prevent it from happening in the future.
        <br /><br />
        If the problem persists, try clearing the cache.  In some cases, this
        can also be a symptom of hardware starting to fail.Unable to load the webpage because your computer entered sleep or
          hibernate mode.  When this happens, network connections are shut
          down and new network requests fail.  Reloading the page should
          resolve this.No webpage was found for the web address: <strong jscontent="failedUrl"></strong>The webpage at <strong jscontent="failedUrl"></strong> has resulted in
          too many redirects.  Clearing your cookies for this site or allowing third-party cookies may fix the problem.  If
          not, it is possibly a server configuration issue and not a problem with your
          computer.Unable to load the webpage because the server sent no data.The response from the server contained duplicate headers.  This problem
        is generally the result of a misconfigured website or proxy.  Only the
        website or proxy administrator can fix this issue.This error can occur when connecting to a secure (HTTPS) server. It
        means that the server is trying to set up a secure connection but, due to
        a disastrous misconfiguration, the connection wouldn't be secure at all!
        <br /><br /> In this case the
        server needs to be fixed.
        <span jscontent="productName"></span>
        won't use insecure connections in order to protect your privacy.Error $1 ($2): $3HTTP Error $1 ($2): $3The operation timed out.The server unexpectedly closed the connection.The connection was reset.The server refused the connection.The attempt to connect to the server failed.A network change was detected.Unable to resolve the server's DNS address.Unable to reach the server.Unable to access the network.Unable to access the file.Proxy server connection failed.The Internet connection has been lost.Error reading data from cache.The requested entry was not found in the cache.Network IO suspended.The file or directory could not be found.There were too many redirects.The server closed the connection without sending any data.Multiple distinct Content-Length headers received.  This is disallowed
        to protect against HTTP response splitting attacks.Multiple distinct Content-Disposition headers received.  This is disallowed to
        protect against HTTP response splitting attacks.Multiple distinct Location headers received.  This is disallowed to protect
        against HTTP response splitting attacks.Unknown error.Access to the webpage was deniedAccess to the file was deniedYou are not authorized to access the webpage at <strong jscontent="failedUrl"></strong>.  You may need to sign in.The server refused to fulfill the request.The webpage at <strong jscontent="failedUrl"></strong> no longer exists.The requested resource no longer exists, and there is no forwarding address.  This is expected to be a permanent condition.Server errorThe website encountered an error while retrieving <strong jscontent="failedUrl"></strong>.
        It may be down for maintenance or configured incorrectly.An unexpected condition was encountered while the server was attempting to fulfill the request.The website is unable to handle the request for <strong jscontent="failedUrl"></strong>.The server does not support the functionality required to fulfill the request.The server does not support the HTTP version used in the request.An invalid response was received while attempting to load <strong jscontent="failedUrl"></strong>.
        The server may be down for maintenance or configured incorrectly.The gateway or proxy server received an invalid response from an upstream server.The webpage at <strong jscontent="failedUrl"></strong> is currently unavailable.  It may be overloaded or down for maintenance.The server is currently unable to handle the request.  This code indicates this is a temporary condition, and the server will be up again after a delay.The server for <strong jscontent="failedUrl"></strong> took too long to respond.  It may be overloaded.The gateway or proxy server timed out while waiting for a response from an upstream server.SSL connection errorUnable to make a secure connection to the server. This may be a problem with the server, or it may be requiring a client authentication certificate that you don't have.SSL protocol error.Incorrect certificate for host.The server presented a certificate that doesn't match built-in expectations. These expectations are included for certain, high-security websites in order to protect you.The server's certificate appears to be a forgery.The SSL renegotiation extension was missing from the secure handshake. For some sites, which are known to support the renegotiation extension, Spark requires a more secure handshake to prevent a class of known attacks. The omission of this extension suggests that your connection was intercepted and manipulated in transit.Certificate-based authentication failedThis server requires a certificate for authentication, and didn't accept the one sent by the
        browser. Your certificate may have expired, or the server may not trust its issuer.
        You can try again with a different certificate, if you have one, or you may have to
        obtain a valid certificate from elsewhere.Bad SSL client authentication certificate.It is likely that the server hosting the webpage has been overloaded or encountered an error.
        In order to avoid letting extensions cause too much traffic and making the situation worse,
        <span jscontent="productName"></span>
        has temporarily stopped allowing requests by extensions to this URL.
        <br /><br />
        If you think this behavior is undesirable, for example, you are debugging your own website, please
        visit <strong>http://dev.chromium.org/throttling</strong>,
        where you can find more information including how to disable the feature.Extension requests to this URL have been temporarily throttled.A third-party extension has blocked access to this webpage.Requests to the server have been blocked by an extension.This webpage requires data that you entered earlier in order to be properly displayed. You can send this data again, but by doing so you will repeat any action this page previously performed. Press Reload to resend that data and display this page.The app is currently unreachable.$1 [$2]Security InformationCertificate informationWhat do these mean?The identity of this website has been verified by $1.$1 ($2)$1, $2 $3$1, $2The identity of $1 at $2 has been verified by $3.unknown nameThe identity of this website has not been verified.The identity of the server you are connected to cannot be fully validated. You are connected to a server using a name only valid within your network, which an external certificate authority has no way to validate ownership of. As some certificate authorities will issue certificates for these names regardless, there is no way to ensure you are connected to the intended website and not an attacker.Unable to check whether the certificate has been revoked.The certificate does not specify a mechanism to check whether it has been revoked.Your connection to $1 is encrypted with $2-bit encryption.Your connection to $1 is encrypted with weak encryption.Your connection to $1 is not encrypted.However, this page includes other resources which are not secure. These resources can be viewed by others while in transit, and can be modified by an attacker to change the look of the page.However, this page includes other resources which are not secure. These resources can be viewed by others while in transit, and can be modified by an attacker to change the behavior of the page.$1 $2The connection uses $1.The connection is encrypted using $1, with $2 for message authentication and $3 as the key exchange mechanism.The connection does not use SSL compression.The connection uses $1 SSL compression.The connection had to be retried using an older version of the TLS or SSL protocol. This typically means that the server is using very old software and may have other security issues.The server does not support the TLS renegotiation extension.Site information$1 will restart in $2 seconds.You should restart $1 now.A special security update for $1 was just applied; you should restart now for it to take effect (we'll restore your tabs).OK - Restart nowDon't restartSSL ErrorProceed anywayBack to safetyYou should not proceed, <strong>especially</strong> if you have never seen this warning before for this site.Security ErrorBackYou cannot proceed because the website operator has requested heightened security for this domain.This frame was blocked because it contains some insecure content.Select a certificateSelect a certificate to authenticate yourself to $1Sign in to Security DevicePlease sign in to $1 to generate a key for $2.Please sign in to $1 to import client certificate from $2.Please sign in to $1 to authenticate to $2 with your certificate.Please sign in to $1.Please sign in to $1 to import the client certificate.Please sign in to $1 to export the client certificate.Password:UnlockExtensionsFonts and encodingStandard fontSerif fontSans-serif fontFixed-width fontMinimum font sizeEncodingTinyHugeLorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.Loading...LanguagesLanguages and inputLanguagesAddRemoveAdd languages and drag to order them based on your preference.Please add another language before removing this one.$1 cannot be displayed in this language$1 is displayed in this languageDisplay $1 in this languageThis language is currently in use for displaying $1.Use this language for spell checkingThis language cannot be used for spell checkingThis language is used for spell checkingRelaunchAdd languageLanguage:Confirm Form ResubmissionThe page that you're looking for used information that you entered. Returning to that page might cause any action you took to be repeated. Do you want to continue?Continue(empty)You can search from here with $1Type to search or enter a URL to navigate - everything just works.ChangeAw, Snap!Something went wrong while displaying this webpage.If you're seeing this frequently, try $1.these suggestionsReloadBrowser DoctorTo continue,or letsolve your problem.He's dead, Jim!Either Spark ran out of memory or the process for the webpage was terminated for some other reason.Send feedback to help improve SparkSpark ran out of memory.
To hide access to this program, you need to uninstall it by using
$1 in Control Panel.

Would you like to start $1?SettingsHide advanced settings...Show advanced settings...BasicsPersonal stuffUnder the hood$1 - $2HelpWebKitMore info...Hide info...AboutRelaunchA web browser built for speed, simplicity, and securityVersion $1FirmwarePlatformChannelStableBetaDev - UnstableYou have switched to the $1 channel.(Auto-refreshing page every $1 seconds.)(To auto-refresh this page use spark://$1/&lt;secs&gt;)Event Log (newest first):Networks:Ethernet Networks:Wi-Fi Networks:Cellular Networks:Virtual Networks:Remembered Wi-Fi Networks:On startupOpen the New Tab pageOpen the home pageReopen the pages that were open lastContinue where I left off.Open a specific page or set of pages.Set pages$1 - $2Add...Add a new pageEnter URL...Startup pagesUse current pagesManage search engines...New Tab pageHome pageHome pageToolbar appearanceHome page:Home page:Use the New Tab pageOpen this page:Show Home buttonChangeAlways show the bookmarks barYour home page has been set.SearchAdd a new search engineKeywordURL with %s in place of queryDefault browserThe default browser is currently $1.$1 is not currently your default browser.$1 cannot determine or set the default browser.This is a secondary installation of $1, and cannot be made your default browser.Launch $1 automatically when I start my computerMake $1 my default browserDownloadsChange...Download location:Download LocationAsk where to save each file before downloadingYou have chosen to open certain file types automatically after downloading.Clear auto-opening settingsChange how $1 handles and displays languagesOffer to translate pages that aren't in a language I readPasswords and formsOffer to save passwords I enter on the web.Offer to save passwordsNever save passwordsManage saved passwordsManage saved passwords...On Mac, passwords are saved to your Keychain and may be accessed or synced by other Chrome users sharing this OS X account.Offer to sign into Google sites automatically with this accountForm autofillPasswordsDo you want Spark to save this credit card information for completing web forms?Enable Autofill to fill out web forms in a single click.Save infoDon't saveDo you want to use Accelarated Autofill?AccelarateNo thanksClear formThis webpage has disabled automatic filling for this form.Automatic credit card filling is disabled because this form does not use a secure connection.Edit...Manage Autofill settingsManage Autofill settings...Add new street address...Add new credit card...Autofill settingsInclude addresses from my Address Book cardAmerican ExpressDiners ClubDiscoverCredit card (other)JCBMasterCardSoloVisaAddressesCredit cardsEdit addressAdd an addressEdit credit cardAdd a credit card, , $1, Exp: $2$1 / $2 bytes, InterruptedFirst nameMiddle name(s)Last nameEmailCompany nameAddress line 1Address line 2City/TownStateAreaCountyDepartmentDistrictEmirateIslandParishPrefectureProvinceZIP codePostal codeCountryPhoneAdd first nameAdd middle name(s)Add last nameAdd phone numberAdd email addressName on cardCredit card numberExpiration dateAbout Autofillheuristic type: $1
server type: $2
field signature: $3
form signature: $4
experiment id: "$5"Help make Autofill better.Send feedback to Baidu.The form signature $1 is for $2.Submit Payment DetailsEditWarning: this site has requested your payment details over an insecure connection.The following details will be shared with $1For your security, please verify your card details.Email addressCredit cardBilling detailsShipping detailsUse billing address for shippingSubmitAuto-Checkout...AppearanceThemesReset to default themeGet themes$1 is using your computer's system proxy settings to connect to the network.Your network proxy settings are being managed by an extension.Google Cloud PrintYou can only edit settings for the current user. Switch to this user to edit settings for it.$1 lets you access this computer's printers from anywhere. Click to enable.Add printersYou have registered your printers with $1 using the account $2Disconnect printersManage print settings...Enabling...Enable phishing and malware protectionEnable automatic password generationComputer-wide SSL settings:Check for server certificate revocationManage your dataBrowsing dataImport bookmarks and settings...This setting is enforced by your administrator.This setting is enforced by an extension.You are following the administrator's recommendation for this setting.Your administrator recommends a specific value for this setting.Follow recommendationThese settings are enforced by your administrator.These settings are enforced by an extension.To make Spark even faster, we've automatically disabled some extensions that may have been added without your knowledge. You can enable or disable any extension below.To make Spark even faster, we've automatically disabled some extensions that may have been added without your knowledge:This extension was automatically disabled.Not from Chrome Web Store.Installed by a third party.... and $1 more.Time for a tune-upYou can always enable or disable any extension in the extension settings page.Extension SettingsOK, GreatSearch resultsNo matches were found.Can't find what you're looking for?$1 helpSearch settingsPredict network actions to improve page load performanceCookies set by this pageThe following cookies were set when you viewed this page:The following cookies were blocked:The following cookies were blocked (third-party cookies are being blocked without exception):AllowClear on exitBlockCookies from $1 allowed.Cookies from $1 blocked.Cookies from $1 will be cleared on exit.Cookies from multiple sites allowed.Cookies from multiple sites blocked.Cookies from multiple sites will be cleared on exit.AllowedBlockedNew cookie settings will take effect after reloading the page.ReloadSign in to this site as: $1Sign inNever offer to sign me inOK, syncNo thanksCreate a new userSign in anywayNow you can access your bookmarks, history, and other settings on all of your signed in devices.UndoOK, got it!UndoAdvancedUse default settingsSign inLearn moreCreate a new userCancelCookies and site dataSearch cookiesRemoveRemove allName:Content:Domain:Path:Send for:Accessible to script:Created:Expires:IntentsSiteApp dataRemove intentWhen the browsing session endsAny kind of connectionSecure connections onlyYesNo (HttpOnly)<no cookie selected>SiteLocally stored data1 cookie$1 cookiesDescription:<unnamed>Key:Value:Origin:Size on disk:Last modified:CookiesApplication cachesApplication cacheFlash dataManifest:Size:Database storageWeb databasesDatabase name:Local storageSession storageIndexed databaseIndexed databasesFile systemFile systemsTemporary storage:Persistent storage:NoneLast accessed:Channel IDChannel IDsDomain:Certificate Type:Created:Expires:rsa_signecdsa_signNew TabMost visitedSuggestedAppsRestore allRecently closedOther devicesAccess your open tabs on all of your devices.http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?answer=185277&hl=enOpen allCollapse listExpand list<strong>You've gone incognito</strong>. Pages you view in this window won't appear in your browser history or search history, and they won't leave other traces, like cookies, on your computer after you close <strong>all</strong> open incognito windows. Any files you download or bookmarks you create will be preserved, however.
          <br /><br />
          <strong>Going incognito doesn't affect the behavior of other people, servers, or software. Be wary of:</strong>
          <ul>
            <li>Websites that collect or share information about you</li>
            <li>Internet service providers or employers that track the pages you visit</li>
            <li>Malicious software that tracks your keystrokes in exchange for free smileys</li>
            <li>Surveillance by secret agents</li>
            <li>People standing behind you</li>
          </ul>Because $1 does not control how extensions handle your personal data, all extensions have been disabled for incognito windows. You can reenable them individually in the
        <a href="$2">extensions manager</a>.<strong>You're browsing as a guest</strong>. Pages you view in this window won't appear in the browser history or search history, and they won't leave other traces, like cookies, on the computer after you sign out. Files you download and bookmarks you create won't be preserved.
          <br /><br />
          <a href="$1">Learn more</a> about Guest browsing.1 Tab$1 TabsTheme created byThumbnail removed.UndoDon't show on this pageUse left and right arrow keys to navigate.Go to $1More $1OptionsView in Web StoreDisable notificationsEnable notificationsAllow notificationsCreate shortcuts...Open as pinned tabOpen as regular tabOpen as windowOpen full screenOpen maximizedAdd more apps$1 would like to send notifications, but you need to be signed in to Spark.Sign in nowNo thanksUsersSwitch UsersSwitch to a different user.Add new userNew usereditCustomize user: $1Switch to user: $1UsersFirst userUser $1Agent XSpandexMiaButtondownSneakyMoonbeamAwesomePetalsSliceFritzPicklesFluffySweetnessSparkySaratogaLemonadeBluesyShadyIcon $1Customize user...Not signed inEnable these features...Add new user...Edit...Delete...Delete this userDisconnect this account...Customize sync settings...Not signed inDefaultAdvancedUse default settingsSign in to $1...Signing in with this username has been disabled by your administrator.This account is already being used on this computer.Signed in as $1Malware Detected!Warning: Something's Not Right Here!Malware Ahead!The Website Ahead Contains Malware!Danger: Malware Ahead!<strong>$1</strong> contains malware. Your computer might catch a virus if you visit this site.Google has found malicious software may be installed onto your computer if you proceed. If you've visited this site in the past or you trust this site, it's possible that it has just recently been compromised by a hacker. You should not proceed, and perhaps try again tomorrow or go somewhere else.If you understand that visiting this site may harm your computer, $1.$1 has blocked access to $2 for now.$1 has blocked access to this page on $2.Even if you have visited this website safely in the past, visiting it now is very likely to infect your computer with malware.Content from $1, a known malware distributor, has been inserted into this web page. Visiting this page now is very likely to infect your computer with malware.Malware is malicious software that causes things like identity theft, financial loss, and permanent file deletion.proceed anywayProceed at your own risk<strong>$1</strong> contains content from <strong>$2</strong>, a site known to distribute malware. Your computer might catch a virus if you visit this site.We have already notified <strong>$1</strong> that we found malware on the site. For more about the problems found on $2, visit the Google $3.AdvancedLearn moreDetails about problems on this websiteDetails about $1Go backSafe Browsing diagnostic pageSafe Browsing privacy policiesPrivacy policyhttp://www.google.com/chrome/intl/en/privacy.htmlHelp improve detection of malware by sending additional data to Google about sites on which you see this warning. This data will be handled in accordance with the $1.Improve malware detection by sending additional data to Google when I encounter warnings like this. $1Phishing Detected!Phishing Ahead!Warning: Suspected phishing site!Reported Phishing Website Ahead!The website at <strong>$1</strong> has been reported as a “phishing” site.  Phishing sites trick users into disclosing personal or financial information, often by pretending to represent trusted institutions, such as banks.$1 has blocked access to $2.  This website has been reported as a phishing website.Learn more about phishing scams.Phishing websites are designed to trick you into disclosing your login, password or other sensitive information by disguising themselves as other websites you may trust.If you feel you understand the risks, you may $1.proceed anywayGo backReport an errorReport an incorrect warningMalware and phishing Detected!The website at <strong>$1</strong> contains elements from sites which appear to host malware – software that can hurt your computer or otherwise operate without your consent.  Just visiting a site that hosts malware can infect your computer. The website also hosts contents from sites that have been reported as a “phishing” sites.  Phishing sites trick users into disclosing personal or financial information, often by pretending to represent trusted institutions, such as banks.Below is a list of all the unsafe elements for the page. Click on the Diagnostic link for more information on the malware thread for a specific resource. If you know that a resource has been erroneously reported as phishing, click the 'Report error' link.The website at <strong>$1</strong> contains elements from sites which appear to host malware – software that can hurt your computer or otherwise operate without your consent.  Just visiting a site that contains malware can infect your computer.Below is a list of all the unsafe elements for the page. Click on the Diagnostic link for more information on the thread for a specific element.Learn more about how to protect yourself from harmful software online.The website at <strong>$1</strong> contains elements from sites which have been reported as “phishing” sites.  Phishing sites trick users into disclosing personal or financial information, often by pretending to represent trusted institutions, such as banks.PhishingMalwareI understand that visiting this site may harm my computer.Proceed anyway$1 is required to display some elements on this page.Install plug-in...Problems installing?Problems updating?$1 was blocked because it is out of date.Run this timeAlways run on this siteTry again$1 has crashed.$1 has encountered an error.Could not load $1.A part of this page (HTML WebWorker) has crashed, so it might not function correctly.Script on the page used too much memory. Reload to enable scripts again.You have never visited this site before today.You first visited this site on $1.External Protocol RequestLaunch ApplicationDo NothingThe following application will be launched if you accept this request:

 $1If you did not initiate this request, it may represent an attempted attack on your system. Unless you took an explicit action to initiate this request, you should press Do Nothing.Remember my choice for all links of this type.Index of LOCATION[parent directory]NameSizeDate ModifiedOh, no! This server is sending data $1 can't understand. Please <a href="http://code.google.com/p/chromium/issues/entry">report a bug</a>, and include the <a href="LOCATION">raw listing</a>.Webpage, HTML OnlyWebpage, CompleteCompletedCancelled$1 / $2 filesContent settings...Clear browsing data...Customize fonts...Change proxy settings...Manage certificates...You may optionally disable these services.Use a web service to help resolve navigation errorsUse a prediction service to help complete searches and URLs typed in the address barUse a web service to help resolve spelling errorsAutomatically send usage statistics and crash reports to BaiduSend a ‘Do Not Track’ request with your browsing trafficEnabling ‘Do Not Track’ means that a request will be included with your browsing traffic. Any effect depends on whether a website responds to the request, and how the request is interpreted. For example, some websites may respond to this request by showing you ads that aren't based on other websites you've visited. Many websites will still collect and use your browsing data - for example to improve security, to provide content, services, ads and recommendations on their websites, and to generate reporting statistics.Do Not TrackOKCancelPressing Tab on a webpage highlights links, as well as form fieldsChange the default font and language for webpages.Page zoom:Font size:Very SmallSmallMediumLargeVery LargeCustomLanguage and input settings...Enable spell checkingEnable automatic spell correctionDownloading spell check dictionary...Spell check dictionary download failed.RetryPlease check with your network administrator to make sure that the firewall is not blocking downloads from Google servers.Your profile could not be opened correctly.

Some features may be unavailable.  Please check that the profile exists and you have permission to read and write its contents.$1 can not be run as root.Please start $1 as a normal user. To run as root, you must specify an alternate --user-data-dir for storage of profile information.Warning: your $1 settings are stored on a network drive. This may result in slowdowns, crashes, or even loss of data.Failed To Create Data DirectoryChoose Another Directory...PrivacyWeb contentHTTPS/SSLNetworkTranslateLanguagesSystemThis site is attempting to download multiple files. Do you want to allow this?AllowDenySearch backgroundsAllCustomCustom Image:Position:Color:Preview:DownloadingYour wallpaper will be shown on the login screens and your background.Your wallpaper will be displayed on your background only.Spark cannot access wallpapers at this time.Spark cannot download this wallpaper.Download was canceled.Spark cannot access the image.Spark cannot set wallpaper.Packaged Files appMake the Files app use new "packaged apps" APIs.FilesArchivesExternal StorageGoogle DriveShared with meRecentOfflineDownloads<strong>Caution:</strong>  These files are temporary and may be automatically deleted to free up disk space.  <a href="javascript://">Learn More</a>NameSize$1 bytes$1 KB$1 MB$1 GB$1 TB$1 PBCtrlAltShiftMetaSpaceEnterTypeDate modifiedPreviewAvailable offlineUnable to create folder "$1". $2Invalid character: $1This name may not be used as a file of folder nameNames starting with dot are reserved for the system. Please choose another name.Invalid namePlease specify a folder nameThis name is too longNew folderFile namePreparing$1 itemsDimensions$1 x $2Image DimensionsVolume LabelRead OnlyUnable to open "$1": $2<b>Don't remove your device just yet!</b>
       <br/><br/>
       Removing your device while it is in use may cause data loss.  Please wait until the operation is over, then eject the device using the Files app.OpenFormat deviceEject deviceCloseViewOpenDocsSheetsSlidesWatchListenOpenNo images in this directory.$1 items selectedMosaic viewSlide viewSlideshowDeleteSend to Google DriveEditSharePress Enter when doneAuto-fixFixedCropBrightnessBrightnessContrastLeftRightUndoRedoFile already existsSavedOverwrite originalYour edits are saved automatically.<br><br>To keep a copy of the original image, uncheck "Overwrite original"Changes are not saved yet.Cannot save to $1. Edited images will be saved in the Downloads folder.This file could not be displayed.This file is too large to be opened.This file could not be played.An error occurred. Click to restart from the beginning.This file could not be played.This image is not available offline.This video is not available offline.This file is not available offline.Import photos to Google DriveGoogle Drive could not be reachedView filesWatch $1Next ›$1 files$1 photosChecking your USB drive...Checking your SD card...Import mediaImporting $1 photos to DriveImport completeImportCancelError accessing "My Photos".Cannot read the photos.Unknown dateNew AlbumWhere to import this photo?Where to import these $1 photos?Cannot import. An error occured.Select photos to importSelect allSelect noneDelete photos after import1 selected$1 selectedA file named "$1" already exists. Do you want to replace it?The file named "$1" already exists. Please choose a different name.The folder named "$1" already exists. Please choose a different name.Unable to rename "$1". $2Enter a new nameRenameUnable to delete "$1". $2DeletePasteCopyCutOpen with...Zip selectionTransferring $1 items.Transfer cancelled.Transfer failed, item exists: "$1"Transfer failed. $1Transfer failed, unexpected error: $1Copying $1Copying $1 items.Copy operation cancelled.Copy operation failed, item exists: "$1"Copy operation failed. $1Copy operation failed, unexpected error: $1Moving $1Moving $1 items.Move cancelled.Move failed, item exists: "$1"Move failed. $1Move failed, unexpected error: $1Zipping $1Zipping $1 items.Zipping cancelled.Zipping failed, item exists: "$1"Zipping failed. $1Zipping failed, unexpected error: $1Deleted $1 itemsDeleted "$1"UndoCancelOpenSaveOKSearchNew FolderShow all filesAre you sure you want to delete "$1"?Are you sure you want to delete $1 items?This device cannot be opened because its filesystem was not recognized.This device cannot be opened because its filesystem is not supported.Formatting the removable media is going to erase all data. Do you wish to continue?Select a folder to openSelect a file to openSelect one or more filesSave file as$1 files selected$1 folders selected$1 items selectedCalculating sizeYou are offlineTo save this file for offline use, get back online and<br>select the '$1' checkbox for this file.To save these files for offline use, get back online and<br>select the '$1' checkbox for these files.You must be online to access this file.You must be online to access these files.Fetching this file will use approximately $1 of mobile data.Fetching these files will use approximately $1 of mobile data.Do not use mobile data for syncShow Google Docs filesClean local cacheReloadHelpBuy more storage...Go to drive.google.com...Google Drive space left: $1.Buy more storageYou have run out of spaceYou have run out of space in Google DriveHang with us. We’re fetching your files.$1 files fetchedGoogle Drive cannot be reached at this time.Learn moreRetryTo save "$1" offline you must free up an additional $2 of space:<br>
        <ul><li>unpin files that you no longer need to access offline</li>
        <li>delete files from your Downloads folder</li></ul>You do not have enough space in Google Drive to save "$1". Please remove files or <a target='_blank' href='$2'>buy more storage space</a>.Welcome to Google Drive!Get 100 GB free with Google DriveGet 1 TB free with Google DriveAll files saved in this folder are backed up online automatically<p><strong>Access files from everywhere, even offline.</strong>
        Files in Google Drive are up-to-date and available from any device.</p>
        <p><strong>Keep your files safe.</strong>
        No matter what happens to your device, your files are safely stored in Google Drive.</p>
        <p><strong>Share, create and collaborate</strong>
        on files with others all in one place.</p>Get startedDismissThis file type is not